["YOU'RE MY FAVORITE SONG"
BY PRINCESS ALIYAH]
Previously on You're
My Favorite Song.
Sell this resort to me, or we're
going to have a problem.
For almost 17 years, Serina,
you never reached out to us.
We've been looking for you.
Why would you even look
for me,
when you already have your
favorite child with you?
Come on, my child.
Stop calling me "child."
Is the story
about the missing princess
of the Montaverde family true?
The Montaverde princess
is truly missing.
I can feel it,
that she's still alive.
And I'm sure
that Celestine inherited
her father's courage
and her mother's intelligence.
On Celestine's first birthday...
[VASE CLATTERS]
She was kidnapped
by unknown men.
When Ma'am Isabella
passed away...
Isabella...
the mansion lost all its color.
For the first time in the
history of Brighton Bay Academy,
someone has answered
my bonus question.
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
Miss Angel Dimaculangan?
- [STUDENTS MURMURING]
- What?
One hundred fifty
out of one hundred.
And I think
we now have a new top student
here at Brighton Bay Academy.
You're supposed to distribute
our test papers, right?
So pick them up.
Let me help you, Angel.
Hopefully you won't drop
it again next time.
Your new house in Solmera
City is beautiful.
I'll continue busking
here in Solmera.
Maybe I'll do it in front
of Brighton Bay Academy.
Who's that girl again?
Angel?
I wonder if I'll see her again.
I just want to busk here.
I'm just hoping, Jacob.
That Angel might be
at Manila Park
since that's where
you met before?
Miguel,
what are you doing here
wearing that stupid costume?
[GRIPPING MUSIC PLAYING]
♪'Cause baby,
you are my favorite song ♪
♪ I'll put you on repeat
all night ♪
♪ I know I'll never move on ♪
♪ My first,
right where I belong ♪
♪ You are my first
heartbeat song ♪
What if someone recognizes you?
Dad, I've been doing this
for months, okay?
And I'm fine.
No one's catching me anyway.
I just want to sing
without anyone recognizing me.
That's who I was before
I became famous, right?
- [CLICKS TONGUE]
- You will not
waste your time like this.
Today is my rest day.
Rest day?
It's your rest day
and you're out singing.
You've got a lot of energy,
so why don't you go back
to the studio,
meet up with your bandmates
and finish your album?
Right?
Jacob, you too.
Sorry, Sir Neil.
Fix this.
I told you.
[POIGNANT MUSIC PLAYING]
You should've listened to me.
[JACOB CLICKS TONGUE]
Can you just behave
for once?
Now your dad's mad.
Charm,
your test paper.
Congrats,
85 out of 100.
We got the same score.
[MELLOW MUSIC PLAYING]
Thank you.
Loser.
- [SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [ADIE CHUCKLES]
Sir Enrico,
- you've been working all week,
- Lady Mara.
The doctor said you need
to rest.
- [SIGHS]
- You know me, Lady Mara.
Ever since Celestine and...
Isabella,
I've devoted all my time to...
the business.
Please don't worry, Sir.
We never stop praying
that Celestine is still alive.
And that one day,
our princess will return.
Thank you.
Sir, would you like some coffee?
- [EXHALES]
- No, Lady Mara.
Could I just have
brandy instead?
Ah, yes, Sir.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
[BOTTLE CORK POPS]
Sir.
Kindly return this.
Thank you.
Unfortunately, my family
still refuses to sell.
And their cheap hotel
is opening in two days.
And your property has the best
sunset view
in all of Solmera City.
If we acquire it,
our investor in Dubai will
definitely be pleased.
- [CLICKS TONGUE]
- I know.
Don't worry, I'll continue
the negotiations.
You're drinking again?
[SIGHS]
Let me guess.
You're thinking about
your child again.
There you go again, Enrico.
Today, marks 16 years since...
Celestine disappeared.
It's not wrong to
keep hoping that even now
she's still alive
and I'll find my child.
- [SCOFFS]
- Oh, my God.
Are you seriously saying that
to my face?
I'm your wife now
and Celestine is presumed dead.
You're just wasting your time.
You can't even give me a child.
Maybe subconsciously,
you don't want to replace her
in your heart
that's why no matter how we try
to have a baby, we can't!
- My God.
- No, no.
Serina, Serina.
[UNEASY MUSIC PLAYING]
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
I don't like her.
She acts like
she's someone important,
when she just got lucky
on the exam.
I know.
What newcomer scores higher than
a perfect score?
It's so unbelievable.
I mean, I wonder what her cheat
code is.
I know.
Just ignore them.
- Siklab!
- [GIGGLES]
This is our row for today.
Did you hear that?
- You heard that, right? Move.
- Oh my! That was intense, girl.
[GIGGLES]
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Do you see?
Do you see his eyes clearly?
Why do you always keep
looking at Charm?
Do you have a crush on her?
- Yeah.
- [CHUCKLES]
No, but...
That's not important.
What matters is you should know
that aside from Calix,
she's someone you shouldn't
mess with.
[SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
What do you mean?
I like them both,
if Calix is super smart...
- Aside from Calix,
- [SOFT TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
she's someone you shouldn't
go up against.
What do you mean?
In our section, there's
a hierarchy everyone follows.
Like I told you earlier,
the seating arrangements here
have meaning.
And that's something you need
to understand, Angel.
If you're seated in row one,
from there to the end,
you're usually considered
one of the "losers."
Like me, a bit shy,
kind of awkward.
[CHUCKLES]
Also those who easily
get panic attacks.
Those with poor eyesight
and frequent illnesses.
In short,
the ones in row one are those
who need special attention
so they can be rushed
to the clinic quickly.
What about me in row two?
That's where Miss Dragona
placed me yesterday.
Your row
is for the smartest students.
That's why you're seated
near Calix.
He's brought many awards
to Brighton Academy.
He's the best student on campus.
But...
it looks like that might be
you now.
Even so.
Calix is still capable of a lot.
Like what?
Like getting everything
he wants.
As for row three,
those are the average students.
The ones who are just okay,
easygoing in life,
those who just
don't want stress.
A lot of them come from
wealthy families.
But they're tight as a group.
If you mess with one of them,
they'll all come
after you together.
[ADIE AND CHARM SQUEALS]
- Oh my gosh, he's so handsome!
- I want to see Miguel in person
at their concert here
in Solmera City.
What?
- He's so handsome, Adie.
- Oh my God, oh, wait.
Oh my gosh.
I thought Calix was your type?
Well,
I like them both.
If Calix is super smart,
then Miguel is super talented.
Imagine, he's not just
the main vocalist,
he's also the writer of all
Siklab's hit songs.
[CHUCKLES]
- Oh my God.
- That's why I like him.
- I like them.
- Oh my gosh, he's so cute.
- Yeah.
- Look at that.
- [CHARM SQUEALS]
- [ADIE GASPS]
And his looks, Siklab.
[ADIE AND CHARM SQUEALING]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Those are Calix's group
in row four.
Row four is the most
hated section.
Because
that's where teachers put
the troublemakers
and the ones
with the lowest grades.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
That's why they all
follow Calix.
Because if Calix didn't
let them copy,
they'd probably
have been expelled from Brighton
Academy a long time ago.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
[EXHALES]
[TYRONE EXHALES]
Do you love me, Serina?
What kind of question is that?
Of course.
But I'm married, Tyrone.
The only thing Enrico
has over me
is that he's a billionaire.
[SCOFFS]
Stop being insecure about that.
You know I was miserable
with him.
He's either busy with work or
grieving for his missing child
who was kidnapped
by a syndicate.
But everything changed
when I met you two years ago.
Honestly, I wish you were
the one in Enrico's place.
Then why don't
we just switch places?
Huh? What do you mean?
Isn't Enrico all alone in life?
And his family is already
torn apart because of business.
So technically,
if something happens to him,
all his wealth will go to you.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Are you suggesting
we kill Enrico?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
I have a lot
of connections, Serina.
It doesn't matter if
Enrico is an army reservist.
I know someone who works clean.
- [CLICKS TONGUE]
- You know what,
let's just go home.
Let's go back to the mansion
before Enrico suspects anything.
And make sure to clean up, okay?
[EXHALES]
[TENSE MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Dad,
our grand opening
is still a day away,
so why do you already
look defeated?
No, my child.
I was just thinking
about Serina.
Her anger toward us
is so intense.
[SOMBER MUSIC PLAYING]
What can we do?
Do you want me to talk
to her, Dad?
I'll tell her about your cancer.
So she'll finally come
to her senses.
I don't want it that way.
Beverly,
I don't want
her to come back to the family
just because she feels
forced to because
I'm sick or because she thinks
I'm dying.
[EXHALES DEEPLY]
I still have a long life
ahead of me.
And if she comes back out
of obligation,
you know
what will happen when I'm gone?
You'll just end up
fighting again.
I want our family
to truly reconcile,
a genuine reconciliation,
where we truly understand
each other.
Not just the two of us,
but you two as well.
All right?
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Here's the payment.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll add more,
just make sure
you do your job well.
Here's the payment.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
I'll add more, just make sure
you do your job well.
Leave it to us, Miss Serina.
Their grand opening
will not happen.
Just make sure of it.
Make sure
you ruin Gran Vista Resort.
Yes, Ma'am.
All right, leave now.
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SERINA EXHALES]
The kids I hired are good.
Even if they get caught,
they won't be jailed
since they're minors.
Thank you, Tyrone.
I'll do anything for you,
Serina.
[UPBEAT MUSIC PLAYING]
Good thing Ma'am Perez
is absent,
we get to hang out here
on the roof deck.
Hey!
You like me, right?
Can you get my water?
Of course.
[UPBEAT MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh no,
where are our bags?
My mom will be so mad
if I lose it.
- [SIGHS]
- That bag is important to me.
Where is it?
Yours is the blue one, right?
Yeah, Yours is the brown one,
right?
Yes.
Hey! Is that it?
- Oh no!
- Why is it here?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Who threw this?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Calix.
Why?
Do you have a problem?
Did you throw this?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Yes.
Got a complaint?
What is your problem?
What did I ever do to you?
I just wanted to check your bag.
Maybe you had cheat notes.
I mean, are you really smart?
Or are you just getting lucky?
Or maybe...
Maybe I'm right.
- That you're cheating!
- I'm not a cheater.
Let's see then.
In the absence
of air resistance,
which force causes all objects
in free fall
to accelerate at the same rate
regardless of mass?
Gravity.
If a species
has no natural predators
and unlimited resources,
what growth pattern
will it show initially?
It will exhibit
exponential growth.
My turn.
If an object
has constant velocity,
what can be said about the net
force acting on it?
The net force is zero.
I know that.
I was just about to answer.
That just means you're slow.
You're not as good
as you think you are, Calix.
Out of all the people
you could go up against here
at Brighton Bay Academy,
you chose me?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
I'm not afraid of you, Calix.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
Wrong answer.
Because you should be.
Do it, Calix.
Punch her.
Yeah, she deserves it.
Go, go.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC INTENSIFIES]
Find out tomorrow on You're My
Favorite Song...
This is the one I wanted.
There, it's simple.
That one.
But that one has already
been sold.
The person who bought it
is someone dear to you.
- Really?
- Yes.
Your wife.
Tell me the truth.
Are you having an affair
with Tyrone?
[GRIPPING MUSIC PLAYING]
[OBJECTS CLATTERING]
Hey!
- Who are you?
- Hey! What are you doing?
[GRIPPING MUSIC CONTINUES]
We'll go through every room
and every door here.
- All right.
- Until I find them.
[PHONE CHIMES]
Hey.
[CHIMING CONTINUES]
It's Mom Bebe.
- [LINE RINGING]
- I wonder why she's calling.
- Hey! My bag!
- For three!
[BAG THUDS]
Wait, This bag...
I know this bag.
There! Someone took my bag,
- Zion.
- ♪ I'm still searching ♪
♪ In case you come back to... ♪